(Sheldon:)No, it's a different Leonard.
(Leonard:)He's...
(Sheldon:)Chinese, red hair, six fingers.
(Sheldon:)Good-bye.
(Leonard:)Raj.
(Sheldon:)Have you seen Howard?
(Raj:)I think he's eating lunch.
(Raj:)Uh, Sheldon, I want you
to meet Neil deGrasse Tyson
(Raj:)from the Hayden Planetarium
in New York.
(Sheldon:)I'm quite familiar
with Dr. Tyson.
(Sheldon:)He's responsible
for the demotion of Pluto
(Sheldon:)from planetary status.
(Sheldon:)I liked Pluto.
(Sheldon:)Ergo I do not like you.
(Dr Tyson:)But I actually
didn't demote Pluto.
(Dr Tyson:)That was a vote
(Dr Tyson:)of the International
Astronomical Union.
If "ifs" and "buts"
were candy and nuts,
(Sheldon:)we'd all have a merry Christmas.
(Sheldon:)Think about that, Dr. Tyson.
(Dr Tyson:)Is that the guy you
were telling me about?
(Raj:)Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)Howard.
(Sheldon:)The person at fault for you
(Sheldon:)not getting
a security clearance is me.
(Howard:)You?
(Sheldon:)Yes, but before you get upset,
I want you to know